Krishna Kumar Pandey

Patna, Bihar, India

krisanunpredictable7@gmail.com

7004079380

linkedin.com/in/krishna-kumar6600

Summary

I am pursuing mba in MARKETING and BUSINESS ANALYTICS from birla institute of technology mesra. I have completed my graduation in bcom from Marwari college ranchi. Worked as trainee in operations team of NIPL with reliance jio.I consider myself as a hardworking person with good communication skills.

Experience



Customer Service Associate

Amazon

Sep 2023 - Feb 2024 (6 months)

- 1. Handling voice call of US retail.
- 2. Handling customer queries of pre-order and post-order queries.

EC Business Analyst Intern

EClytics Consulting

Feb 2023 - Mar 2023 (2 months)

- 1.Creating dashboard in business intelligence tools for analyzing data in Power BI and Excel.
- 2.Perform dax queries and functions in power BI.
- 3.Used advanced excel to create pivot table and lookups function.
- 4. Analyze data and present it through reports that can help in decison making.

Business trainee

ICICI Prudential Life Insurance Company Limited

Jul 2021 - Aug 2022 (1 year 2 months)

Worked as business trainee in patna location. Looked after new business generation and documentation of investment and insurance business in banca channel.



\lambda Digital Marketing Intern

Augmenting Times

Aug 2020 - Sep 2020 (2 months)

Digital Marketing intern at Augmenting Times

Education



BIT Mesra Student-Industry Relations Cell

Master of Business Administration - MBA, Marketing and Business analytics 2019 - 2021

Marwari College

Bachelor of Commerce, bcom accounts hons 2016 - 2019

saraswati shishu vidya Mandir

12th, commerce 2014 - 2016

Skills

Scrum • Dashboards • Computer Science • Canva • Customer Interaction • Knowledge Acquisition • VBA Excel • Quantitative Analytics • Financial Data • Microsoft Word